

PROFILE

Recent coding bootcamp graduate seeking an entry level full stack web development position in a collaborative, fast paced environment where I can contribute, learn and grow from experienced professionals.

3 years experience in music production, property management and guest relations, gaining valuable transferable skills in relationship building, strategic planning and project management.

Strong record of quickly learning and adapting to new and complex situations.

Eager to leverage a diverse range of talents in a new and engaging professional setting. Committed to lifelong learning and personal development.

CONTACT

iakemeeks21@gmail.com



P Denver, CO

in https://linkedin.com/in/jacob-meeks

https://github.com/JakeAwsd

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Music production Song writing Acting Hiking Weight lifting Coding

JACOB MEEKS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Music Production - Self Employed

2020-Present

Self-taught musician. Placement on Spotify Playlist. Proficient in Ableton, Fruity Loops, Reason Studios and Streamlabs. Proficient with the marketing platforms Twitch, Spotify, SoundCloud and Distrokid.

Iphone Repair - Self Employed

2018-Present

Basic Iphone repair services. Self-taught

Wilhelmina – 2021- Present

Talent/Modeling/Acting

Wellspring Capital / Park Real Estate Group - Assistant

2019-Present Denver, Colorado

Assisting in family owned Real Estate and Property Management company on a part time basis. Repairs, remodels, landscaping and customer service. Developed valuable skills in customer satisfaction, project management and work flow.

Gaylord Rockies Resort & Convention Center – Seasonal - Usher

October 2021 - January 2022 Denver, CO

Interacted with 1000's of people daily to ensure a great holiday experience. Kept service areas clear and sanitized, and swept after every showing of the Cirque show. Responsible for handling tricky situations when they arose. Developed a new method to clean and sort seat coverings which optimized workflow by 20%

EDUCATION

University of Denver 2021-2022

Computer Science - Full Stack Web Development Certificate 24 Week Coding Bootcamp

Northfield High School 2021 Graduate

KEY SKILLS

- React
- **i**Query
- HTML
- Heroku
- CSS
- Git

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- BootStrap
- **Express**
- MongoDB
- MERN Stack
- MySQL